Sync and corrected by
rickSG www.addic7ed.com
♪ I'm goin' down to South
Park, gonna have myself a time ♪
♪ Friendly faces everywhere ♪
♪ Humble folks without temptation ♪
♪ Goin' down to South Park,
gonna leave my woes behind ♪
♪ Ample parking day or night ♪
♪ People spouting, "Howdy, neighbor!" ♪
♪ Heading on up to South Park,
gonna see if I can't unwind ♪
♪ Mrph rmhmhm rm! Mrph rmhmhm rm! ♪
♪ Come on down to South Park
and meet some friends of mine ♪
PC PRINCIPAL: All right,
everyone. Listen up.
Today, we're gonna be
showing you some art
from our Asian-American
students, and...
Damn it, Leslie! Shut
your [bleep] pie hole!
From our Asian-American students
presented by student-body president,
Wendy Testaberger.
Hey, guys.
As you know, we have
several new students
here at South Park Elementary.
We have been getting to
know some of the Asian girls,
who have introduced us to
an art style called "yaoi."
Yaoi is a blend of emotion and beauty
involving two people whose
love is looked down upon.
The art tries to show
that all love is magical,
like in Lisa Akimoto's piece,
"Tweek and Craig: Forbidden Love."
[Girls "Aww"]
What?!
Kelly Zhou goes a bit more whimsical
with "Craig and Tweek Moonlight Dance."
[Girls "Aww"]
Dude, what the [bleep]?
In yaoi art, the  seme,  or "top,"
Is usually dominating In is usually
dominating the  uke,  or "bottom,"
as demonstrated in Heather Nishimura's
"Tweek and Craig: Boizu Rabu."
"[Girls "Aww" and applause]"
But yaoi can branch out
to other things, as well...
Uh-oh.
As we see here in "Lilly,
Frog, Tweek, and Craig."
I just don't get it.
I mean, Tweek and
Craig aren't gay, right?
No. We would know.
Well, but then why would Asian
girls draw them like that?
Yeah, what is this yaoi thing all about?
I'm so co-confused.
And if it can happen to Tweek and Craig,
Could it happen to any of us?
Uh, excuse me. Why are you doing this?
Oh, hi, Craig.
[Speaking Korean]
What? What did she say?
I don't know. That was
Korean. I'm Japanese.
What is going on, huh?!
Me and him aren't together!
Why is this happening?!
[Speaking Korean]
Everyone thinks I'm gay!
What if my parents find out?! Aah!
PC PRINCIPAL: All right, guys, I know
there's been a lot of rumors flying around.
Just wanted to check in, see if
you have any questions for me.
Why are the Asian girls drawing
pictures of us being gay?
What's wrong with being
gay? Nothing wrong with that.
But we aren't. I'm not.
I'm not either!
That is completely irrelevant, okay?
What matters, and the
reason I brought you in here,
Is that you understand
affirmative consent.
What's that?
If there is a romantic
relationship here,
You have to make sure
your partner is comfortable
With any sexual exploration.
Aah!
Now, in a gay relationship,
it gets a little trickier,
But you still have to follow
some guidelines, all right?
But I'm not gay!
I don't care about that, bro!
Tweek, if... and I'm only saying if...
At some point, you wanted
to touch Craig's penis,
You can't just go
grabbing for it, all right?
You would need to say something like,
"Craig, is it all right with
you if I touch your penis?"
Okay? Let's try it out.
No!
You want two weeks detention instead?!
This shit's important!
Craig, can I touch your penis?
Okay. Good. Now, Craig, you might say,
"You may touch my penis.
I'm comfortable with that."
Or, of course, you could say,
"No, you may not touch
my penis at this time."
No, you may not.
Okay. Now we're getting somewhere.
Now, Craig, what would you say
If you wanted to take a
gander at Tweek's asshole?
Randy, you should have a talk with Stan.
For what?
I guess something
happened at school today
Involving two of Stan's
friends [whispers] being gay.
What?
Yeah, Stan seems really perplexed.
Wow.
Our town has only had a
Whole Foods for three weeks,
And we already have our first gay kids.
So cool.
Go talk to him, Randy, and be delicate.
Hey, bud.
How's it hanging?
I'm confused, Dad. There
was this thing at school.
Well, guess what.
You've got a really progressive P.C. dad
Who knows all about this stuff, okay?
Go ahead. Ask me anything.
I just don't understand
how it's decided.
Ah, well, you see, it's a combination
Of genetic, hormonal, and
environmental influences.
No, I mean, like, what
makes the Asians decide
Who they're gonna make gay?
The Asians?
The Asians decide who's gonna be gay?
Uh, uh, yeah. Yeah, they do.
Uh, the Asians just, you know...
They just pick who they pick,
And, um, so it's the
way it's always been.
So, you've heard of yaoi?
[Chuckles] Yeah, of course.
Yaoi, anal intercourse, Maui Zaui.
I-I know all this stuff, Stan.
Oh, hey, Thomas!
Hey, we heard about Craig.
We think it's just terrific.
What about Craig?
Thomas, I'm so glad that
Craig is finally happy.
Hey! It's Craig's dad, everybody!
[Scattered applause]
Tweek's out of coffee, honey.
Oh, here you go, kiddo.
Tweek, is there anything
you want to talk to us about?
No.
Well, we heard that you're gay.
And I want you to know we've
never been so proud of you.
Oh, God!
We thought you were just a spaz,
But to know you've got
so much going on inside...
We're so proud of you, Tweek.
[Groans]
Knowing what I know now,
I'm gonna be a much better dad to you.
In fact, I just...
I just want to give
you some money, Tweek.
Can I give you some money?
Here. I-I love you so much, son.
♪ The Book of Love
is long and boring ♪
♪ No one can lift the damn thing ♪
♪ It's full of charts
and facts and figures ♪
♪ And instructions for dancing ♪
♪ But
I-I-I-I-I-I ♪
♪ I love it when you read to me ♪
♪ And
you-u-u-u-u-u ♪
♪ You can read me anything ♪
♪ The Book of Love has music in it ♪
♪ In fact, that's
where music comes from ♪
♪ Some of it's just transcendental ♪
♪ Some of it's just really dumb ♪
♪ But
I-I-I-I-I-I ♪
♪ I love it when you sing to me ♪
♪ And
you-u-u-u-u-u ♪
♪ You can sing me anything ♪
CARTMAN: [Thinking]
Dude, Tweek and Craig.
It's just so weird.
If they've been gay this whole time,
Have they been checking me out?
I'm pretty sure Craig
has seen my wiener.
Should I kick his ass?
[Twinkle!] Oh, come on!
What's wrong with two
guys liking each other?
I just don't understand it, Cupid Me.
Wanting to, like, kiss a dude?
But if love is love,
Then it takes form in all
shapes and sizes. Tee hee!
I guess just because
I don't understand it
Doesn't mean I shouldn't support it.
All right.
Maybe you can help them along.
Really? Can I?
Yes, Cupid Me. Make it quick.
Don't let anyone see you.
Oh, thank you! I will!
Tee hee hee! Tee hee hee hee!
Tee hee hee!
[Snoring]
Tee hee hee! Tee hee!
You just need a little spark of magic.
[Twinkle!] Tee hee hee!
And now I'm gonna pee in your mouth.
[Chuckles] Love is in the air!
[Twinkle!]
Did you do it, Cupid Me?
I hit him with my love arrow,
And then I peed in
his mouth just for fun.
[Laughs] That's awesome!
That's so sweet! [Chuckles]
I thought you might like that.
Yeah, dude. You're hilarious.
And do you think I'm cute, too?
'Cause I think you're kind of cute.
Stop that, Cupid Me.
I told you I'm not homosexual,
okay? It's not funny.
Oh, well. At least Tweek
and Craig are in love now.
Yep. School tomorrow should
be really interesting.
And so then my dad
talked to me about it.
And my dad says Asians
have always done this,
And they, like, do make people gay.
- You guys! You guys! Hurry!
- What?
It's... It's Tweek and Craig, dude!
They're about to have sex!
You got a [bleep] problem, man?
You're the one with the [bleep] problem!
I told you to stay 100 yards from me!
You better not [bleep]
push me again, man!
Oh, God, you guys. Get a room.
[Cheering]
Hello. Mr. Tucker?
I need to inform you that your son
was in an altercation at school today.
Craig? Craig got in a fight?
Yes, with his boyfriend.
Just a lovers' quarrel, probably.
God damn it.
Something to be expected
in relationships.
Apparently, there were no
affirmative-consent issues,
as your son knows the right way
to play with another boy's penis.
Oh, God.
There's not gonna be
any disciplinary action.
Since they are gay, we
want to be supportive.
So, we're just gonna send them on
home with some money, all right?
All right, you have a nice day.
Money?
[Chinese music plays]
[Speaking Chinese]
[Sighs]
Uh, hi. Mr. Jinping?
Thanks for taking my call.
I was just wondering if
you could shed some light
On how your people
decide who will be gay
And who will be straight.
[Chinese accent] What?!
I'm sorry. I-I don't
speak Asian, but, um...
Oh, uh... Oh!
Y-Yaoi. Yaoi, yes?
Boyzu love-u.
H-How does that work?
That come from Japan.
Oh, it's Japan that decides?
How the hell do they
actually make people ga...
And Japan, of course,
Is who does the yaoi to make people gay.
They are dogs who refuse not apologize
To the Chinese Republic!
Uh-huh. Yes. That, of course,
I do already know about homosexuality.
[Doorbell rings]
Hi. Flower delivery for Eric Cartman.
Oh, my. How beautiful!
Oh, look, sweetie!
Someone sent you flowers.
CARTMAN: "Can't we just try? TeeHee."
Oh, man.
Who are they from, hon?
Someone who needs a
real talking to. [Sighs]
Look, it's flattering, okay?
But it doesn't change the fact
That there's nothing here
for you to keep pursuing.
Tee hee hee! Aw, come on.
Let's be like Tweek and Craig.
Everyone thinks they're cute.
You are wasting your time.
I'm not attracted to guys.
But I'm so attracted to you.
I realize that, and I'm sorry.
I need you to stop bothering me.
This... is done.
I'm just not a homosexual.
[Doorbell rings]
Well, hello, Craig.
Honey, it's Craig.
Aww, hi, Craig.
Is Tweek home?
He sure is. Come on in.
Would you like to have
some coffee, Craig?
No, thank you. I just want to see Tweek.
Aww.
Tweek's just up in his room playing.
You can go on up.
Oh, uh, but keep the
door open, all right?
They're so gay.
Aargh! Aah! Unh!
Aah!
Hey, dude.
[Spits] Aah!
No! No! What are you doing here?
Tweek, calm down. We have
to put a stop to this.
There's no stopping it!
The whole world wants me
to be something I'm not!
Me, too, dude. But there's
something we can do.
What?!
We have to come out and say we're gay.
What?! Are you insane?!
Tweek, Tweek. Because, if
we're gay, then we can break up.
And if we break up, no more pictures.
We just have to stage a fake breakup
In front of the Asian girls.
Like acting?! No, man. That
is way too much pressure.
You can do it, Tweek.
You're capable of more than you think.
Ugh! I'm a terrible actor.
You just follow my lead and try
and make it believable, okay?
Oh, God. Okay. Oh, God!
What did I do wrong, huh?
Everyone's so damn happy,
But... but why did this
have to happen to my son?
What did I do to make my son like this?
Hey, hey, whoa. You didn't do anything.
Oh, what? You know about this?
Yeah, let me handle this, guys. I'm P.C.
Look, Thomas, you need to understand
that being gay isn't a decision.
You know, a lot of people
think that Asians decide
Who's gay and who's not.
But it isn't all Asians.
It's just specifically
the Japanese, okay?
What?
Why do the Japanese make some
people gay and others not?
Well, it goes back to World War II
And atrocities that
happened in China called
The Rape of Don King.
Well, you sure know a lot about this.
Yes, I do.
No, dude. I looked it up.
Yaoi is just an art
style for girls by girls
Because they like fictionalizing
two guys in a relationship.
- But why?
- I don't know.
But the point is, there's nothing
about it that means Tweek and Craig
Are actually gay at all.
Hey, Tweek. Hold up.
Listen, it's just not going to work.
What?! Why not?!
I'm sorry, Tweek, but we
can't lie to ourselves anymore.
Yes, we are gay. But we
do not belong together.
We don't belong together?
What suddenly changed, Craig?
It's just that people
are different. That's all.
Uh-huh. And who the hell is Michael?
Huh? You want to tell me that?!
Uh, what are you... what
are you talking about?
I went through your phone when
we went out last night, Craig.
I saw your text to Michael
about hooking up with him!
Wait, uh... t-that's not what happened.
Oh, it's not?!
No. L-look, we both know
this is for the better.
Oh, don't use that lame shit on me, man.
You don't want to feel bad, so
you try and tell me what I want?!
Tweek, don't make me out
to be the bad guy here.
No, you're not the bad guy.
You're never the bad guy, are you?!
You... you just step on
people and you use them!
You're going too far, dude. This
is, like, totally not necessary.
I'm going too far?!
What is wrong with you?!
This wasn't part of the plan.
Well, guess what, Craig?!
Love doesn't follow a plan!
Yeah!
I was totally wrong about you.
I opened myself up and let you in,
But you've got spikes, man.
You've got spikes.
[A Great Big World's
"Say Something" playing]
Tweek!
Dude, seriously? Seriously?!
[Thunder rumbles]
♪ Say something ♪
♪ I'm giving up on you ♪
They... they broke up?
♪ I'll be the one
if you want me to ♪
♪ Anywhere, I would
have followed you ♪
♪ Say something ♪
♪ I'm giving up on you ♪
[Music ends]
[Whispering] What are you doing?
This place isn't you.
I'm just here to pick up on guys.
Why? Are you jealous?
No, I'm not.
I'm here because we need you right now.
Oh, now you need me, huh?
[Bleep] you, dude.
[Bleep] you.
What is that kid doing here?
He's just kind of talking to himself.
The whole town is sad.
Cupid Me, you have to help.
Well, I guess I could try and help.
In return for just one date?
I'm not homosexual!
Then I guess I'm not interested.
[Sighs] All right. One date.
But only if you help get
Tweek and Craig back together.
Tee hee hee! Tee hee hee hee hee!
Hey, kid, what do you
think you're doing here?
Oh, oh, hey, whoa. Whoa, whoa, whoa.
I'm not here for me. I'm
here for my friend, okay?
[Doorbell rings]
Hi. Is Craig here, sir?
Why can't you quit him?
Thomas.
Five minutes. He's in the back.
Hey, dude.
What do you want?
I thought when we broke up
everything would get better.
I was thinking maybe we
should say we're back together.
Dude, I'm not gay, and neither are you!
What does that have to do with anything?
You think you can just pull
that shit you pulled at school,
Saying I step on people and use them,
And I'll just take you back?
You said to make it seem real.
Not that real!
Now everyone thinks I'm
a manipulative cheater.
I'll never get any chicks.
I'm so sorry, Craig.
You... you made me believe in
myself in a way I never have before.
I didn't think I had any of
that in me, but you were right.
I can do more than I think.
You changed something
in me, and I just...
I want to fix whatever's
hurting you now.
[Sobbing]
I can't be something because
everyone wants me to be.
I have to be myself.
You'll just have to go
be gay with someone else.
All right, Craig. All right.
I can see how much they're
both hurting, but...
Can't you understand that in my
time we just didn't accept this?
Maybe it's not so wrong.
I... I just don't want it to be my son.
[Wings beating]
Tee hee hee! Tee hee hee!
You just need a little prick of magic.
[Twinkle]
I'm gonna pee in your
mouth a little bit.
[Trickling]
Then again, he's my son, no matter what.
I can't just shut down on him.
Tee hee hee! Tee hee hee hee!
[Wings beating]
Son, you need to listen to me.
You can't fight being gay.
I used to think that
being gay was a choice,
But you don't get to decide.
Japan picks who they
pick, and that's that.
I don't understand this stuff.
Heck, I didn't even
know Don King got raped,
But I do know that if
you try and resist it,
You make yourself
miserable your whole life.
Everyone was so proud of you.
I was just being selfish. I
want to be proud of you, too.
I like gay Craig. I love you.
Here's $100.
[Wistful music playing]
MAN: [Japanese accent] ♪
Maybe we should go away ♪
♪ Put cares aside for just a day ♪
♪ The world we face is not so big ♪
♪ Not if we are strong
like Tweek and Craig ♪
[Speaking Japanese]
♪ Let's go back to when it was new ♪
♪ Weren't we such
happy people, too? ♪
♪ Life was simple, problems vague ♪
♪ We had it all, a lot
like Tweek and Craig ♪
♪ And in the darkness we all seek ♪
♪ A perfect love
like Craig and Tweek ♪
_
Highest honor!
Gambaro irashai!
♪ I hope you know,
when you are down ♪
♪ That you turned my life around ♪
♪ Just like the like the
quote from Shakespeare said ♪
♪ I'm your Tweek ♪
♪ And you're my Craig ♪
[Moaning]
Okay, okay. The date's almost over.
Tee hee hee!
Aren't you liking your massage?
It's fine. It just doesn't
really do anything for me.
[Speaking Japanese]
Well, I've got something you
might like a little better.
Cupid... Cupid Me, no!
No! I'm straight!
Tee hee hee hee!
Cupid Me, what are
you doing? Oh, my God!
Oh, Cupid Me, that's enough!
Okay, that's it, Cupid Me! That's it!
That's it, Cupid Me. Okay, that's it.
That's it, Cupid Me.
Aww.
Sync and corrected by rickSG
www.addic7ed.com