I called earlier about a missing
U.S. citizen in the Middle East.
How are you, Sara?
I wanted the State Department, not you.
Any chance Poseidon will
just let us kill her?
SARA: I've learned some things
about who it is we're
apparently both looking for.
C-NOTE: You think Michael's in Yemen?
- We're gonna get you out of here.
- I don't know who you are.
C-NOTE: Your brother was using
this shop for his escape.
We're here for passports.
[screams]
[grunts]
Figure we got a day to
get out of this hole.
We're still getting out. All of us.
_
Poseidon put us in
here to get Ramal out,
but then he abandoned us.
Ramal's Poseidon's guy, not ours.
Our friend told me about the escape.
He will betray you.
MICHAEL: When those lights go black,
we're gonna disappear from
this place like ghosts.
I can't get it open.
Help me out.
You pull my brother up first.
[screams]
[yelling in Arabic]
Don't shoot.
- [explosion]
- _
- Hey.
How are you feeling?
Body is fine.
My head is
trying to figure out how
to get those passports
we couldn't get last night.
For you, those kids.
Well, that's something you shouldn't
be worrying about right now.
You should rest up.
We're gonna need you.
I can rest when I'm dead.
Well, that's what I'm worried about.
Didn't know you worried.
About the right things.
Your brother.
He make it out?
- I'm sorry.
- Yeah.
Sheba, do you mind if I
borrow Linc for a second?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Please get some rest.
[indistinct speaking over hospital PA]
Listen. We got to start talking
about leaving the country.
What are you talking about?
I spoke to my friends at the mosque.
ISIL is taking
neighborhoods by the hour.
If they cut off the
route to the airport...
I'm not leaving Michael.
If they cut off the airport,
no one is getting out.
Not you, me, Sheba.
As much as it kills me to say...
we can't risk all of it for...
just one man.
You're right.
You can leave.
But I can't.
Get that family to the
airport as fast as you can.
I'll work something out.
Mr. Burrows?
I wanted to thank you
for saving my daughter.
And offer you something in appreciation.
I might have a solution
for how to get your brother
out of that prison.
[explosion]
Before the city goes to hell.
_
[men shouting]
You hear that?
That was the closest one yet!
100 yards!
Just when you think
it couldn't get worse
locked up in a Porta Potti,
they start dropping 2,000-pound
bombs on the Porta Potti.
MICHAEL: Whip. Keep it together, please.
The escape artist is nervous.
MICHAEL: You should be, too.
Those artillery strikes,
they don't discriminate.
The difference is I have faith.
Allah will deliver me.
What do you have?
Ja!
Ja, are you there?
I'm here.
[explosion]
Whip's right.
The strikes are getting closer.
I pity you.
I triumph either way.
Either I will be in paradise
or Allah will save me.
You,
you're just going to die.
[indistinct conversations]
ISIL has broken through the checkpoints.
They're coming into the city.
These uniforms are like targets
- on our backs.
- ISIL isn't here yet.
The government says
it will push them back.
You out of your head? This is happening.
Sana'a is falling.
They're going to retreat.
I've seen that look before in the army.
Men who will do anything
to save themselves.
And how do we save ourselves?
ISIL takes this prison, we'll
be the first they slaughter.
When they take this prison, it will be
to liberate their leader, Ramal,
but if when they get here,
we have him with a knife
to his throat,
then we call the shots.
And we might just live.
MICHAEL: Whip, I got a Hail Mary.
- That a prayer or a plan?
- Plan.
I left something the
last time I was in here.
Let me guess, you got a contingency.
They lock me away in
a box for four years.
I'm not just gonna sit there.
It's a long shot, but
it might get us out.
ABU RAMAL: The infidel
still tries to escape.
The desperate rat.
The desperate rat's gonna light you up
once we get out of here,
- you bugged-eyed freak.
- MICHAEL: Whip.
Whip! An "S." Is there an "S"
carved in your wall chest high
in the corner?
Come on, come on.
That's not it.
I'm not seeing anything.
I'm not seeing it.
Ja, it's got to be you.
Come on. Tell me you got
an "S" carved in your wall.
It's our last chance.
No.
It's not here, no.
[laughing]
[whispering]: That's
because I have it in my cell.
[explosion]
My armies of the caliphate
are coming closer.
The moment they reach this place,
all of you will be put down
like the dogs that you are.
♪ ♪
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
... www.Addic7ed.com ...
_
♪ ♪
[phone beeps]
T-BAG: All right, Sara.
Our friend, Poseidon, has surfaced.
[car engine starts in the distance]
JAMIL: Good God.
Another ISIL attack.
They're ripping the city apart.
They're animals.
I've been a bureaucrat my whole life.
Hated it.
Corruption, backslapping.
But today, maybe some
good will come of it.
I went to grammar school with this boy
named Ibrahim.
All the years later,
he's a federal judge.
You, uh, saying this judge can help us?
I called him a few
hours ago and told him
about your brother's case.
- [gunshot in the distance]
- _
JAMIL: Redecorating, I see.
Just readying for the
coming change of seasons.
Luxury is something the
Wahabbists frown upon,
so luxury will stay behind closed doors.
You should flee the country.
I'm a survivor, you know that.
I thought Mr. Burrows could perhaps
help with his brother's cause.
Ah, yes.
A full pardon from the
Supreme Judicial Council.
But you will have to uphold
your end of the bargain,
Jamil.
German engineering. 77,000 miles.
Five liter, seven speed, V10.
It will be a welcome bit of luxury.
Behind closed doors, of course.
Best of luck to both of you.
I really appreciate this.
- Thank you.
- [car door closes]
It's already done.
It would've been left behind anyhow.
May both of our families
get safely out of Sana'a tonight.
[explosion]
WHIP: We can't just sit here and die.
You-you got a window
like this one, right?
Maybe we can pry it.
It's too small, reinforced.
Built into the rebar infrastructure.
You got people on the outside, right?
And they're gonna try and get us out.
They were supposed
to meet us at the shop
last night and we didn't show.
We can't just quit
- and let Poseidon beat us.
- Ramal?
There's a way out if we work together,
but escape has to start from your cell.
I'm no longer interested.
The only thing left
for you to do is to beg.
Beg that I might let you
live once my armies came,
if only as a slave.
I've been a slave for
the last seven years.
I won't do it anymore!
[soft chuckle]
I will miss you when you're dead,
but only for a minute.
Then you will be forgotten
by both time and the world.
KELLERMAN: Well, she's
my kid, too, Cindy.
I have the weekends and...
Well, no, I have the weekends
and I don't want a Wednesday afternoon.
Why would I want that?
Yeah, nobody does.
[soft creaking]
Uh-huh.
No, that's okay, Cindy.
[gun cocks]
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, that's fine.
What other days?
What other days do you want?
Actually, you know what?
I don't want to discuss this now.
No, we'll talk about it later.
Bye.
Of all the things
that mystify me in this world
since I've been released,
is that kale is the rage.
Kale.
- [chuckles]
- Theodore Bagwell.
Thing that mystifies me equally
is seven years ago,
you exonerated Michael,
Lincoln, all of them,
except me.
[laughs, then grunts]
- Really?
- Yes!
That's why you're here?
Because I didn't exonerate you?
A murderer,
a sexual predator a dozen times over.
"Was" is the key word.
I'm a man moving toward the light now,
and the light's beckoning me.
I just don't know who's
pulling the strings.
But Sara says it's you.
Oh, Sara put you onto me?
Okay.
I don't know who the bigger idiot is,
you or her.
I was helping her.
You were hacking her phone
and sending those people
after her... Don't...
lie.
[sighs]
Now...
how about you pour me one of
them nasty little kale jobbies,
and tell me what's all this got
to do with Scofield and myself,
who your friends are,
who you are... I want to see
the true face of who's
pulling my strings
once and for all.
[knocking]
You have two visitors in the lobby.
Tell them I'll be right down.
[clears throat]
Hey.
I got this, Grace.
[gunfire and shouting in distance]
They're in the city.
What are you doing?
What do you think I'm doing?
Don't run, you dog!
Don't run!
It is happening. Be ready.
[indistinct shouting]
[woman screaming]
This pardon better get him out of here.
We don't have much time... we
have to get to the warden.
JAMIL: What's going on?
[excited chatter, shouting]
[speaking Arabic]
They're abandoning the
prison. That's why Ibrahim
gave us that pardon.
He knew it was worthless.
You and C-Note get the
others to the airport
as fast as you can...
There's maybe one flight out.
Save two seats.
All right?
What are you going to do?
I'm gonna get my brother.
[men shouting, clamoring]
MAN: Mustapha!
Back up!
Back up. Anyone comes at me, dies.
- Understand?
- You think you can shoot all of us?
Anyone else want to play the lottery?
Huh? You're filth.
I'll let ISIL sort you out.
ZAKAT: Mustapha!
Mustapha! Mustapha, wait!
Don't lock me in here!
You coward.
Mustapha, please.
Coward!
- I need to get in!
- I need to get out!
- Well, give me the key.
- I don't have the key.
You passed the guy who does.
[men clamoring, gunfire in distance]
[panting]
[missile whistling through air]
[woman screaming]
[indistinct shouts]
Stay back! I don't want to shoot you!
[indistinct shout]
[pounding on door]
The guards are gone!
They're abandoning their posts!
We're gonna be free!
No. We're not free.
Things just got a lot worse.
MAN: Push the gate open!
Stop! Stop!
What are you doing?
- We have to get through the gate!
- If ISIL controls the city,
like they say, it will be
a prison out there as well.
We will be persecuted,
as we have been in here, only worse!
At least there's a chance!
You want a chance?
Our chance lies in there,
in solitary.
Our bargaining chip.
We get Abu Ramal!
We negotiate passage
out of the country.
No, it's madness.
Come on. If we work together,
we can push open the gate.
Is that you, Princess?
It is you. We remember this one!
- Right? We remember him!
- Please...
Friend to Kaniel Outis,
the man who would not
lend my brother a hand!
The man who killed my brother,
as far as I'm concerned, right?
- We are going to go in there and get Abu Ramal!
- No! Please!
- And when we are there,
I am personally going to
slice Kaniel Outis' throat.
And you are going to be the one
who's going to help me do it.
- No!
- You sent him!
- [men yelling]
- Take him!
All of you!
Will you stay here?
And let ISIL slaughter you?
Or will you stand with me?
And fight!
[men yelling]
Doesn't sound very promising!
Ramal,
you want to rethink helping us?
Escape has to start
from your cell!
All you infidels can go to Hell!
We are in Hell, Ramal.
Question is do you want out?
- Smash through the door!
- [men clamoring in agreement]
Tell me what to do.
MAN: Come on, come on...
[woman screams]
[men shouting in Arabic]
[man shouting in Arabic]
_
- _
- [gun cocks]
_
KELLERMAN: I'm not hacking
anybody's phones.
You're so off base on this,
you have no idea.
Am I? [chuckles]
Y-Yes.
[spits] That is terrible,
by the way. What is that,
an act of contrition?
Like a hair shirt?
Torture yourself with kale
to make up for your sins?
I don't have any sins anymore, man.
- That's you.
- How about the sin of deceit?
Hmm?
A kale-drinking man named
Kellerman by the light of day,
a murderous CIA rogue
named Poseidon at night.
Poseidon?
[whoops] His eyes light up.
She was right.
Oh, you think I'm Poseidon?
[laughing]: Okay.
Are you mixed up with Poseidon?
Oh, hell,
we got to go old school with this?
Is that what you want?
- T-Bag snapping fingers.
- Ow!
That's very... you just gave
me something to work with.
Poseidon? Poseidon.
[scoffs]
I'll tell you about Poseidon.
I mean, he's one of those myths
you hear about in the system.
He's an operative so untouchable,
so deep, you couldn't find
him with a nuclear sub.
Hence the nickname.
And how does this involve me?
What's he want with Michael?
[banging]
MICHAEL: Ramal, listen closely.
The brick with the "S," it's loose.
You got to remove it.
[shouting, clamoring outside]
It's a spoon, string.
- How?
- A string a day from
my uniforms for four years.
A spoon a guard overlooked
one time in a thousand.
There's a water pipe above you.
Hook it, pull it down.
Do it!
Hey. Let me get this straight.
This is getting him out?
MICHAEL: It's getting us all out.
This is a two-cell job, mine and his.
That's why I couldn't pull it off
when I was in that cell,
because the guy across from me,
the guy in this cell,
wouldn't cooperate.
[echoing]: We have to work together.
Come on!
- No.
- Cross!
I'm not working with you.
No. No.
- [yells]
- Come here! Come on, sweetheart.
Show them your pretty
face! Come on, get up here!
Look! Stop what you're doing
and tell Kaniel Outis
I will kill the girl!
[yells]
Take him!
Come on! I'm not through with you yet!
They're beating the crap
out of Sid. They'll kill him
- unless we surrender.
- If we surrender,
they'll kill us. They only want Ramal.
Our best chance of saving
Sid is getting out of here.
Make them forget about
him, start chasing us.
Okay, good.
Now pick it up. String the cord
and pull it through.
[man yelling, banging on wall]
Come on, come on!
Yeah!
I will kill the girl, I swear it!
No!
[automatic gunfire]
[anxious chatter]
I will say it again,
there will not be any
killing in this prison!
Not on my watch!
WHIP: This is completely insane.
It's a freakin' Mexican
soap opera out here!
Ramal, don't stop. Don't start thinking.
Don't pin your hopes on one guard.
Walk away!
Hide in the cell block!
What are you doing?
The prison is done, brother.
For the love of God!
For the love of God,
a man seeks justice.
In everything he does, at all times!
Now, everybody, back in the block!
There are no prisoners
and guards anymore!
You realize that, right?
If ISIL gets in here,
we are all the enemy.
Sinners,
deviants...
and those that locked up their leader.
You will be the only
guard that they catch.
The noble one.
They will behead you for it. But...
if we work together,
we get Ramal,
we have a bargaining chip.
I will see to it
that you will get out
with the rest of us.
Just give me the keys to solitary.
I don't have the keys.
I know you do.
Join us
and you will live.
I give you my word.
I don't have them.
- [grunting]
- [prisoners cheering]
Kill him!
[cheering]
But you have something much better, huh?
Move. Move!
WHIP: Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. They killed the guard!
They got his gun. They're coming for us!
Got to make this count, Ramal.
String that fishing
pole through that slot.
That's right.
Now, you can remove the pinions
on my door... the hinges.
There are two of them.
No way.
What are you doing?
I'm doing mine.
We don't have time for this, Ramal!
I'm telling you, it's a two-cell job,
that's the point. That side of the wing
is new construction. The pinions
are covered in the hinges...
You can't pull them.
This side is original.
They're open, loose.
You want me to free you?
Yes, and I, in turn, free you
with those keys, down there.
Why would I trust you more
than the madman out there?
'Cause you just heard
what his word is worth.
Kick it.
[thumping]
This is it. It's all
about whose word you trust.
I promise you... you release me,
I release you.
Little more, little more.
Thank God. Come on.
Okay, the bottom.
Yes!
[thumping continues]
Come on,
- come on. Come on.
- Come on.
Yes!
Almost there!
[grunting]
WHIP: Yes.
Come on.
[thumping]
Got to hurry up, come on.
Yes. Yes, come on!
RAMAL: Where are you going?
Open my door.
I'm getting the hell out of here.
RAMAL: Open my door.
- Leave him, man, you crazy?
- Open my door.
Once we're outside these walls, we need
safe passage out of the country.
Even now, you negotiate.
[door straining]
We work together or we both die.
You have my word.
Open the door.
[mouths]
We got to go now.
[clamoring, banging]
[cheering]
[indistinct chatter]
No, no!
[indistinct conversations]
KID: Mr. Tic Tac.
What are you doing here?
You gonna fight ISIL men?
Get out of here, kid, hide!
- This is no place for you.
- You gonna fight ISIL men?
Yes.
Listen very closely, all right?
American! American!
American!
[speaking Arabic] _
_
- You go to Bubble Gum Man now?
- Yeah.
Thanks for your help. Here, take that.
Get somewhere safe, okay?
Mr. Tic Tac goes to Bubble Gum Man!
[indistinct chatter]
CROSS: Ramal... don't want to kill you.
Just your friends. You understand?
What are we doing in here?
This is not helping us.
You're gonna make a phone call
so you can hold up your end of the deal.
There's an auto body
shop off Nashwan plaza.
I want vehicles there, full tanks of gas
so we can get to the border, all of us.
I'm not going with you to the border.
MICHAEL: You don't have a choice.
We're gonna ride to the
border, then say sayonara.
You're our insurance.
CROSS: Ramal, I don't want to kill you.
You understand?
Or would you rather be
their insurance? Take it.
[buttons beeping]
[speaking Arabic]
I want to know what he's
saying. He could be screwing us.
He's screwing with us, all right.
We just need to screw with him first.
Where's Ja?
I don't know.
[Ja coughing]
- Oxycodone...
- Hey, we got to peel.
Percocet...
Come on, you Japanese
junkie son of a bitch.
I'm Korean, you Canadian monkey.
Canadian? Oh, that's really funny, Ja.
You'd split my sides if we
weren't about to be slaughtered.
Hey, remember what Woody Allen said.
What did he say?
"I don't mind dying.
I just don't want to be
around when it happens."
Hey, come on.
We need you, okay?
MICHAEL: What's the holdup?
[door opens]
_
KELLERMAN: Scofield's a dead man.
He's tangling with Poseidon.
I see what you're doing here.
Talking Poseidon in third person,
like you're not him.
State Department has been
looking for Poseidon for years,
you idiot. He's a rogue CIA operative.
Nobody knows who he is.
- Here we go.
- I know it's a little
above your pay grade
being a common criminal.
I mean, we're talking
about a single man.
Right? A hawk
who apparently doesn't
like how the White House
goes about foreign policy,
and decided to take
matters into his own hands.
Not with armies, not with invasions,
but by getting a single person killed,
by getting a single
person elected to office,
by getting a single person
released from prison.
Prison, like the one in
Yemen, where Michael's at.
You want my guess?
It's Abu Ramal that Poseidon wants free.
Guy I seen on the prison telly.
Wait, I thought the CIA was
supposed to kill terrorists,
- not release them.
- Poseidon is no longer CIA.
He doesn't report to anybody.
He just pursues his own ideology.
Okay, for instance, listen.
Let's say you think Russia and Iran
are having too much
influence in the Middle East,
and you don't think Washington
is getting the job done.
You free Ramal.
Sure, he's an Islamic radical nut job,
but he will fight Iran
and Russia for you.
The enemy of my enemy is my friend.
And what's so shrewd about Poseidon
is he does it all without a network,
which is why he's so hard to find.
One man can pull strings like that?
One man manipulating
a handful of others.
Abu Ramal is a monster.
And there's a spot in
Hell reserved for him,
but the hottest spot is
reserved for Poseidon,
because he is letting Ramal
loose on the world again.
Those men, they have
the blood of thousands,
thousands on their hands.
Compared to them, you and
me are a couple of angels.
[quiet laugh]
- "Angels"?
- Mm-hmm.
You find out who Poseidon is,
and how Scofield is wrapped up in it,
maybe your fate...
is to be a patriot.
[gunshots through silencer]
What...?
- [gunshot]
- [shouts, grunting]
Go. Go!
[chuckles]
There's a time for everything.
911? I need help... now.
[men shouting]
MICHAEL: They're going over the top.
Let's go.
Go, go, go, go, go!
This way!
It's locked!
It's a dead end.
No, no, no, no. No. No, no, no, no.
Ramal?
[indistinct, overlapping shouting]
Hide! Hide!
I don't want to kill
you! Just your friends.
- You understand?
- Sid, you're alive?
- SID: We'll see about that.
- Ramal?!
Let's hand the son of a bitch over.
Won't work.
They'll gun us down anyway.
Can't just wait here and die.
[panting]
Your game is up.
Come out!
[indistinct, overlapping shouting]
[feet shuffling on floor]
[groans, thuds]
Anyone
who gets between me and Abu Ramal dies.
You understand?!
Where is Ramal?
Tell me now!
[man speaking Arabic]
[Michael panting]
There's a boy.
Ithaca, New York. Mike Scofield.
If I don't make it out of here alive,
tell him his father loves him very much.
[quietly]: "His father"?
[Michael sighs]
If I don't smother that gun,
they'll kill us all.
[both yell]
[gunfire, Cross yelling]
[Cross groaning and panting]
[screaming]
♪ ♪
[men shouting]
[rattling, men shouting]
Move back!
Move back! Go!
Let me through!
[men shouting]
Michael! Michael!
[men shouting, clamoring]
Michael? Michael!
[sighs]
Poseidon sent you?
Where's your friend?
He's long gone.
Back door.
Locked from the inside.
VAN GOGH: He's in here.
Find him.
[panting]
I was you once, killing for a lie.
Now you're what?
Dying for the truth?
It's human nature to find stuff out,
so you will.
Or she will.
And then the lie has to kill the truth.
Which one of you is gonna die ne...?
[casing clinks on floor]
[distant siren wailing]
Time to get scarce.
Hey!
[sirens wailing]
What did he say to you?
Nothing.
[engine starts]
[sirens wailing]
[panting]
Auto shop's a few blocks up.
And your men better be coming.
They will be there.
Where is Ja?
Ja,
- what are you doing?
- I'm starving, man.
You know how long it's
been since I seen fruit?
MICHAEL: You're stopping to eat?
Are you high?!
Don't come at me, man.
You're not my mama.
You know what? You're done.
- You're gone.
- What?
- Wait.
- I said, walk! You're a liability!
Wait. Wait. You said you'd get me out,
all the way home. That was the deal.
[both grunt]
MICHAEL: Ramal, this man follows us,
tell your men to shoot him.
Gladly.
_
[crowd chatter]
LINCOLN: Where'd you go, Michael?
Where'd you go?
[groans, panting]
_
[groans]
[door opens]
_
[panting]
There you are, my men.
Seize these dogs so that
we can put them down.
_
Ramal.
Ramal, what are you doing?
You thought you tricked me?
Take the long way around
while your friend...
gets here first to get weapons.
You were going to screw me.
That's the American slang.
- Isn't it?
- You were gonna screw me.
So much for our word.
Lying to enemies.
It's called Taqiyya.
Take off the camera.
I will show the world
what happens
when you screw Abu Ramal.
On your knees!
- It's not gonna happen.
- Make them on their knees!
[men speaking Arabic]
[grunting]
Enough!
[men speaking Arabic]
Drop your weapons.
[panting]
Step away from my brother.
Linc.
How much do you love
this brother of yours?
[sighs]
Why don't you step down from that truck?
Stop. Stop, stop, stop.
No, it's not going down
like this, okay? Just...
stop. I got way too many
questions for my friend here.
- Step back!
- I went to prison for killing
a guy in a bar fight. I didn't even want
to get into it, okay? He
starts talking yang to my girl.
I tell him to beat it.
He pulls a knife, and I see red.
One second later,
I'm holding his bloody knife,
and it's his body on the ground.
- You're not that fast.
- One second.
Please don't do this.
You will lose.
Listen to your friend.
I'm talking to you, Ramal.
I told you! Step down from that truck.
Pick up your weapons!
You've got one second till
that one second happens.
- Go to hell.
- [groans]
[shouting in Arabic]
[loud groaning]
[engine rumbling nearby]
[tires squealing]
We got more coming!
- WHIP: And more over here!
- This is a big problem.
WHIP: Let's get the hell out of here.
[rapid gunfire]
_
[groans]
[groans softly]
[sighs]
- A&W: You wanted to see us?
- Ouch.
Come on. Come on.
[panting]
[camera shutter clicking]
Behold the villain.
[sighs]
[indistinct shouting]
Who the hell is this guy?
He's my brother.
[voice breaking]: He's my brother.
I can't believe this.
I just can't believe
this. I can't believe this.
Back at the prison. Why?
- Why did you say?
- I had to deny you.
You were... you were filming me.
- They can't know.
- Who can't know?
- They can't know I'm getting out.
- Who?
I'll explain everything later, just...
Sara and-and Mike?
They're good.
- They're fine.
- Oh, thank God.
Thank God.
Questions just keep piling up, huh?
- That's you.
- [man speaking Arabic on TV]
SID: It's all of us.
What are they saying?
That ISIL has taken over
the government station.
That their beloved leader, Abu Ramal,
has been martyred.
That we're the ones that did it.
The entire army of ISIL
just declared war on us.
♪ ♪
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
... www.Addic7ed.com ...